module.exports = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "color: #000;",
      "answer": "black",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "color: #111;",
      "answer": "near-black",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "color: #333;",
      "answer": "dark-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "color: #555;",
      "answer": "mid-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "color: #777;",
      "answer": "gray",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "color: #999;",
      "answer": "silver",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "color: #aaa;",
      "answer": "light-silver",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "color: #ccc;",
      "answer": "moon-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "color: #eee;",
      "answer": "light-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "color: #f4f4f4;",
      "answer": "near-white",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "color: #fff;",
      "answer": "white",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "color: #e7040f;",
      "answer": "dark-red",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "color: #ff4136;",
      "answer": "red",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "color: #ff725c;",
      "answer": "light-red",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "color: #ffdfdf;",
      "answer": "washed-red",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "color: #ff6300;",
      "answer": "orange",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "color: #ffb700;",
      "answer": "gold",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "color: #ffd700;",
      "answer": "yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "color: #fbf1a9;",
      "answer": "light-yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "color: #fffceb;",
      "answer": "washed-yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "color: #5e2ca5;",
      "answer": "purple",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "color: #a463f2;",
      "answer": "light-purple",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "color: #d5008f;",
      "answer": "dark-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "color: #ff41b4;",
      "answer": "hot-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "color: #ff80cc;",
      "answer": "pink",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "color: #ffa3d7;",
      "answer": "light-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "color: #137752;",
      "answer": "dark-green",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "color: #19a974;",
      "answer": "green",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "color: #9eebcf;",
      "answer": "light-green",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "color: #e8fdf5;",
      "answer": "washed-green",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "color: #001b44;",
      "answer": "navy",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "color: #00449e;",
      "answer": "dark-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "color: #357edd;",
      "answer": "blue",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "color: #96ccff;",
      "answer": "light-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "color: #cdecff;",
      "answer": "lightest-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "color: #f6fffe;",
      "answer": "washed-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.9);",
      "answer": "black-90",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.8);",
      "answer": "black-80",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7);",
      "answer": "black-70",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.6);",
      "answer": "black-60",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.5);",
      "answer": "black-50",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.4);",
      "answer": "black-40",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.3);",
      "answer": "black-30",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2);",
      "answer": "black-20",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);",
      "answer": "black-10",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05);",
      "answer": "black-05",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.025);",
      "answer": "black-025",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "black-0125",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.9);",
      "answer": "white-90",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.8);",
      "answer": "white-80",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.7);",
      "answer": "white-70",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.6);",
      "answer": "white-60",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.5);",
      "answer": "white-50",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.4);",
      "answer": "white-40",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.3);",
      "answer": "white-30",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.2);",
      "answer": "white-20",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.1);",
      "answer": "white-10",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.05);",
      "answer": "white-05",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.025);",
      "answer": "white-025",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "white-0125",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "question": "color: transparent;",
      "answer": "transparent",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "question": "color: inherit;",
      "answer": "color-inherit",
      "categories": [
        "Color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#color"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "question": "color: #000;",
      "answer": "hover-black:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "question": "color: #111;",
      "answer": "hover-near-black:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "question": "color: #333;",
      "answer": "hover-dark-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "question": "color: #555;",
      "answer": "hover-mid-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "question": "color: #777;",
      "answer": "hover-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "question": "color: #999;",
      "answer": "hover-silver:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "question": "color: #aaa;",
      "answer": "hover-light-silver:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "question": "color: #ccc;",
      "answer": "hover-moon-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "question": "color: #eee;",
      "answer": "hover-light-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "question": "color: #f4f4f4;",
      "answer": "hover-near-white:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "question": "color: #fff;",
      "answer": "hover-white:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "question": "color: #e7040f;",
      "answer": "hover-dark-red:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "question": "color: #ff4136;",
      "answer": "hover-red:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "question": "color: #ff725c;",
      "answer": "hover-light-red:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "question": "color: #ffdfdf;",
      "answer": "hover-washed-red:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "question": "color: #ff6300;",
      "answer": "hover-orange:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "question": "color: #ffb700;",
      "answer": "hover-gold:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "question": "color: #ffd700;",
      "answer": "hover-yellow:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "question": "color: #fbf1a9;",
      "answer": "hover-light-yellow:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "question": "color: #fffceb;",
      "answer": "hover-washed-yellow:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "question": "color: #5e2ca5;",
      "answer": "hover-purple:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "question": "color: #a463f2;",
      "answer": "hover-light-purple:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "question": "color: #d5008f;",
      "answer": "hover-dark-pink:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "question": "color: #ff41b4;",
      "answer": "hover-hot-pink:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "question": "color: #ff80cc;",
      "answer": "hover-pink:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "question": "color: #ffa3d7;",
      "answer": "hover-light-pink:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "question": "color: #137752;",
      "answer": "hover-dark-green:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "question": "color: #19a974;",
      "answer": "hover-green:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "question": "color: #9eebcf;",
      "answer": "hover-light-green:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "question": "color: #e8fdf5;",
      "answer": "hover-washed-green:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "question": "color: #001b44;",
      "answer": "hover-navy:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "question": "color: #00449e;",
      "answer": "hover-dark-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "question": "color: #357edd;",
      "answer": "hover-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "question": "color: #96ccff;",
      "answer": "hover-light-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "question": "color: #cdecff;",
      "answer": "hover-lightest-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "question": "color: #f6fffe;",
      "answer": "hover-washed-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.9);",
      "answer": "hover-black-90:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.8);",
      "answer": "hover-black-80:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7);",
      "answer": "hover-black-70:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.6);",
      "answer": "hover-black-60:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.5);",
      "answer": "hover-black-50:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.4);",
      "answer": "hover-black-40:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.3);",
      "answer": "hover-black-30:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2);",
      "answer": "hover-black-20:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);",
      "answer": "hover-black-10:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 108,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05);",
      "answer": "hover-black-05:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 109,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.025);",
      "answer": "hover-black-025:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 110,
      "question": "color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "hover-black-0125:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 111,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.9);",
      "answer": "hover-white-90:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 112,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.8);",
      "answer": "hover-white-80:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 113,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.7);",
      "answer": "hover-white-70:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 114,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.6);",
      "answer": "hover-white-60:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 115,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.5);",
      "answer": "hover-white-50:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 116,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.4);",
      "answer": "hover-white-40:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 117,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.3);",
      "answer": "hover-white-30:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 118,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.2);",
      "answer": "hover-white-20:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 119,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.1);",
      "answer": "hover-white-10:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 120,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.05);",
      "answer": "hover-white-05:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 121,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.025);",
      "answer": "hover-white-025:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 122,
      "question": "color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "hover-white-0125:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 123,
      "question": "color: transparent;",
      "answer": "hover-transparent:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 124,
      "question": "color: inherit;",
      "answer": "hover-color-inherit:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 125,
      "question": "background-color: #000;",
      "answer": "bg-black",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 126,
      "question": "background-color: #111;",
      "answer": "bg-near-black",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 127,
      "question": "background-color: #333;",
      "answer": "bg-dark-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 128,
      "question": "background-color: #555;",
      "answer": "bg-mid-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 129,
      "question": "background-color: #777;",
      "answer": "bg-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 130,
      "question": "background-color: #999;",
      "answer": "bg-silver",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 131,
      "question": "background-color: #aaa;",
      "answer": "bg-light-silver",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 132,
      "question": "background-color: #ccc;",
      "answer": "bg-moon-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 133,
      "question": "background-color: #eee;",
      "answer": "bg-light-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 134,
      "question": "background-color: #f4f4f4;",
      "answer": "bg-near-white",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 135,
      "question": "background-color: #fff;",
      "answer": "bg-white",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 136,
      "question": "background-color: #e7040f;",
      "answer": "bg-dark-red",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 137,
      "question": "background-color: #ff4136;",
      "answer": "bg-red",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 138,
      "question": "background-color: #ff725c;",
      "answer": "bg-light-red",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 139,
      "question": "background-color: #ffdfdf;",
      "answer": "bg-washed-red",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 140,
      "question": "background-color: #ff6300;",
      "answer": "bg-orange",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 141,
      "question": "background-color: #ffb700;",
      "answer": "bg-gold",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 142,
      "question": "background-color: #ffd700;",
      "answer": "bg-yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 143,
      "question": "background-color: #fbf1a9;",
      "answer": "bg-light-yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 144,
      "question": "background-color: #fffceb;",
      "answer": "bg-washed-yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 145,
      "question": "background-color: #5e2ca5;",
      "answer": "bg-purple",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 146,
      "question": "background-color: #a463f2;",
      "answer": "bg-light-purple",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 147,
      "question": "background-color: #d5008f;",
      "answer": "bg-dark-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 148,
      "question": "background-color: #ff41b4;",
      "answer": "bg-hot-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 149,
      "question": "background-color: #ff80cc;",
      "answer": "bg-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 150,
      "question": "background-color: #ffa3d7;",
      "answer": "bg-light-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 151,
      "question": "background-color: #137752;",
      "answer": "bg-dark-green",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 152,
      "question": "background-color: #19a974;",
      "answer": "bg-green",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 153,
      "question": "background-color: #9eebcf;",
      "answer": "bg-light-green",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 154,
      "question": "background-color: #e8fdf5;",
      "answer": "bg-washed-green",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 155,
      "question": "background-color: #001b44;",
      "answer": "bg-navy",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 156,
      "question": "background-color: #00449e;",
      "answer": "bg-dark-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 157,
      "question": "background-color: #357edd;",
      "answer": "bg-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 158,
      "question": "background-color: #96ccff;",
      "answer": "bg-light-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 159,
      "question": "background-color: #cdecff;",
      "answer": "bg-lightest-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 160,
      "question": "background-color: #f6fffe;",
      "answer": "bg-washed-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 161,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.9);",
      "answer": "bg-black-90",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 162,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.8);",
      "answer": "bg-black-80",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 163,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7);",
      "answer": "bg-black-70",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 164,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.6);",
      "answer": "bg-black-60",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 165,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.5);",
      "answer": "bg-black-50",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 166,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.4);",
      "answer": "bg-black-40",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 167,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.3);",
      "answer": "bg-black-30",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 168,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2);",
      "answer": "bg-black-20",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 169,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);",
      "answer": "bg-black-10",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 170,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05);",
      "answer": "bg-black-05",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 171,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.025);",
      "answer": "bg-black-025",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 172,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "bg-black-0125",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 173,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.9);",
      "answer": "bg-white-90",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 174,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.8);",
      "answer": "bg-white-80",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 175,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.7);",
      "answer": "bg-white-70",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 176,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.6);",
      "answer": "bg-white-60",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 177,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.5);",
      "answer": "bg-white-50",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 178,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.4);",
      "answer": "bg-white-40",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 179,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.3);",
      "answer": "bg-white-30",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 180,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.2);",
      "answer": "bg-white-20",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 181,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.1);",
      "answer": "bg-white-10",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 182,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.05);",
      "answer": "bg-white-05",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 183,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.025);",
      "answer": "bg-white-025",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 184,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "bg-white-0125",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 185,
      "question": "background-color: transparent;",
      "answer": "bg-transparent",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 186,
      "question": "background-color: inherit;",
      "answer": "bg-color-inherit",
      "categories": [
        "Background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 187,
      "question": "background-color: #000;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 188,
      "question": "background-color: #111;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-near-black:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 189,
      "question": "background-color: #333;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-dark-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 190,
      "question": "background-color: #555;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-mid-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 191,
      "question": "background-color: #777;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 192,
      "question": "background-color: #999;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-silver:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 193,
      "question": "background-color: #aaa;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-light-silver:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 194,
      "question": "background-color: #ccc;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-moon-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 195,
      "question": "background-color: #eee;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-light-gray:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 196,
      "question": "background-color: #f4f4f4;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-near-white:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 197,
      "question": "background-color: #fff;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 198,
      "question": "background-color: #e7040f;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-dark-red:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 199,
      "question": "background-color: #ff4136;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-red:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 200,
      "question": "background-color: #ff725c;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-light-red:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 201,
      "question": "background-color: #ffdfdf;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-washed-red:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 202,
      "question": "background-color: #ff6300;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-orange:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 203,
      "question": "background-color: #ffb700;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-gold:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 204,
      "question": "background-color: #ffd700;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-yellow:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 205,
      "question": "background-color: #fbf1a9;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-light-yellow:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 206,
      "question": "background-color: #fffceb;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-washed-yellow:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 207,
      "question": "background-color: #5e2ca5;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-purple:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 208,
      "question": "background-color: #a463f2;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-light-purple:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 209,
      "question": "background-color: #d5008f;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-dark-pink:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 210,
      "question": "background-color: #ff41b4;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-hot-pink:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 211,
      "question": "background-color: #ff80cc;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-pink:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 212,
      "question": "background-color: #ffa3d7;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-light-pink:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 213,
      "question": "background-color: #137752;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-dark-green:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 214,
      "question": "background-color: #19a974;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-green:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 215,
      "question": "background-color: #9eebcf;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-light-green:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 216,
      "question": "background-color: #e8fdf5;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-washed-green:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 217,
      "question": "background-color: #001b44;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-navy:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 218,
      "question": "background-color: #00449e;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-dark-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 219,
      "question": "background-color: #357edd;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 220,
      "question": "background-color: #96ccff;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-light-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 221,
      "question": "background-color: #cdecff;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-lightest-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 222,
      "question": "background-color: #f6fffe;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-washed-blue:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 223,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.9);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-90:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 224,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.8);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-80:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 225,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-70:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 226,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.6);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-60:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 227,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.5);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-50:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 228,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.4);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-40:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 229,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.3);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-30:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 230,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-20:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 231,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-10:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 232,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-05:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 233,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.025);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-025:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 234,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-black-0125:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 235,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.9);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-90:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 236,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.8);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-80:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 237,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.7);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-70:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 238,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.6);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-60:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 239,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.5);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-50:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 240,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.4);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-40:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 241,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.3);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-30:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 242,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.2);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-20:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 243,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.1);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-10:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 244,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.05);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-05:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 245,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.025);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-025:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 246,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "hover-bg-white-0125:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 247,
      "question": "background-color: transparent;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-transparent:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 248,
      "question": "background-color: inherit;",
      "answer": "hover-bg-color-inherit:hover",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 249,
      "question": "transition: background-color 0.15s ease-in-out;",
      "answer": "bg-animate",
      "categories": [
        "Hover-background-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#hover-background-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 250,
      "question": "background-attachment: scroll;",
      "answer": "bg-scroll",
      "categories": [
        "Background-attachment"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-attachment"
    },
    {
      "id": 251,
      "question": "background-attachment: fixed;",
      "answer": "bg-fixed",
      "categories": [
        "Background-attachment"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-attachment"
    },
    {
      "id": 252,
      "question": "background-attachment: local;",
      "answer": "bg-local",
      "categories": [
        "Background-attachment"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-attachment"
    },
    {
      "id": 253,
      "question": "-webkit-background-clip: text; background-clip: text;",
      "answer": "bg-clip-text",
      "categories": [
        "Background-clip"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-clip"
    },
    {
      "id": 254,
      "question": "background-position: top;",
      "answer": "bg-top",
      "categories": [
        "Background-position"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-position"
    },
    {
      "id": 255,
      "question": "background-position: center;",
      "answer": "bg-center",
      "categories": [
        "Background-position"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-position"
    },
    {
      "id": 256,
      "question": "background-size: cover;",
      "answer": "bg-cover",
      "categories": [
        "Background-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 257,
      "question": "background-size: contain;",
      "answer": "bg-contain",
      "categories": [
        "Background-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 258,
      "question": "background-repeat: no-repeat;",
      "answer": "bg-no-repeat",
      "categories": [
        "Background-repeat"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#background-repeat"
    },
    {
      "id": 259,
      "question": "-o-object-fit: contain; object-fit: contain;",
      "answer": "contain",
      "categories": [
        "Object-fit"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#object-fit"
    },
    {
      "id": 260,
      "question": "-o-object-fit: cover; object-fit: cover;",
      "answer": "cover",
      "categories": [
        "Object-fit"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#object-fit"
    },
    {
      "id": 261,
      "question": "-o-object-fit: fill; object-fit: fill;",
      "answer": "fill",
      "categories": [
        "Object-fit"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#object-fit"
    },
    {
      "id": 262,
      "question": "-webkit-user-select: none; -moz-user-select: none; user-select: none;",
      "answer": "user-select-none",
      "categories": [
        "User-select"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#user-select"
    },
    {
      "id": 263,
      "question": "-webkit-user-select: all; -moz-user-select: all; user-select: all;",
      "answer": "user-select-all",
      "categories": [
        "User-select"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#user-select"
    },
    {
      "id": 264,
      "question": "-webkit-user-select: text; -moz-user-select: text; user-select: text;",
      "answer": "user-select-text",
      "categories": [
        "User-select"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#user-select"
    },
    {
      "id": 265,
      "question": "aspect-ratio: 1;",
      "answer": "ratio-1x1",
      "categories": [
        "Aspect-ratio"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#aspect-ratio"
    },
    {
      "id": 266,
      "question": "aspect-ratio: 16 / 9;",
      "answer": "ratio-16x9",
      "categories": [
        "Aspect-ratio"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#aspect-ratio"
    },
    {
      "id": 267,
      "question": "border-style: solid; border-width: 1px;",
      "answer": "ba",
      "categories": [
        "Border"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border"
    },
    {
      "id": 268,
      "question": "border-top-style: solid; border-top-width: 1px;",
      "answer": "bt",
      "categories": [
        "Border"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border"
    },
    {
      "id": 269,
      "question": "border-right-style: solid; border-right-width: 1px;",
      "answer": "br",
      "categories": [
        "Border"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border"
    },
    {
      "id": 270,
      "question": "border-bottom-style: solid; border-bottom-width: 1px;",
      "answer": "bb",
      "categories": [
        "Border"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border"
    },
    {
      "id": 271,
      "question": "border-left-style: solid; border-left-width: 1px;",
      "answer": "bl",
      "categories": [
        "Border"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border"
    },
    {
      "id": 272,
      "question": "border-style: none; border-width: 0;",
      "answer": "bn",
      "categories": [
        "Border"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border"
    },
    {
      "id": 273,
      "question": "border-width: 0.125rem;",
      "answer": "bw1",
      "categories": [
        "Border-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 274,
      "question": "border-width: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "bw2",
      "categories": [
        "Border-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 275,
      "question": "border-width: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "bw3",
      "categories": [
        "Border-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 276,
      "question": "border-width: 1rem;",
      "answer": "bw4",
      "categories": [
        "Border-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 277,
      "question": "border-width: 2rem;",
      "answer": "bw5",
      "categories": [
        "Border-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 278,
      "question": "border-color: #000;",
      "answer": "b--black",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 279,
      "question": "border-color: #111;",
      "answer": "b--near-black",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 280,
      "question": "border-color: #333;",
      "answer": "b--dark-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 281,
      "question": "border-color: #555;",
      "answer": "b--mid-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 282,
      "question": "border-color: #777;",
      "answer": "b--gray",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 283,
      "question": "border-color: #999;",
      "answer": "b--silver",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 284,
      "question": "border-color: #aaa;",
      "answer": "b--light-silver",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 285,
      "question": "border-color: #ccc;",
      "answer": "b--moon-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 286,
      "question": "border-color: #eee;",
      "answer": "b--light-gray",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 287,
      "question": "border-color: #f4f4f4;",
      "answer": "b--near-white",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 288,
      "question": "border-color: #fff;",
      "answer": "b--white",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 289,
      "question": "border-color: #e7040f;",
      "answer": "b--dark-red",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 290,
      "question": "border-color: #ff4136;",
      "answer": "b--red",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 291,
      "question": "border-color: #ff725c;",
      "answer": "b--light-red",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 292,
      "question": "border-color: #ffdfdf;",
      "answer": "b--washed-red",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 293,
      "question": "border-color: #ff6300;",
      "answer": "b--orange",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 294,
      "question": "border-color: #ffb700;",
      "answer": "b--gold",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 295,
      "question": "border-color: #ffd700;",
      "answer": "b--yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 296,
      "question": "border-color: #fbf1a9;",
      "answer": "b--light-yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 297,
      "question": "border-color: #fffceb;",
      "answer": "b--washed-yellow",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 298,
      "question": "border-color: #5e2ca5;",
      "answer": "b--purple",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 299,
      "question": "border-color: #a463f2;",
      "answer": "b--light-purple",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 300,
      "question": "border-color: #d5008f;",
      "answer": "b--dark-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 301,
      "question": "border-color: #ff41b4;",
      "answer": "b--hot-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 302,
      "question": "border-color: #ff80cc;",
      "answer": "b--pink",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 303,
      "question": "border-color: #ffa3d7;",
      "answer": "b--light-pink",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 304,
      "question": "border-color: #137752;",
      "answer": "b--dark-green",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 305,
      "question": "border-color: #19a974;",
      "answer": "b--green",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 306,
      "question": "border-color: #9eebcf;",
      "answer": "b--light-green",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 307,
      "question": "border-color: #e8fdf5;",
      "answer": "b--washed-green",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 308,
      "question": "border-color: #001b44;",
      "answer": "b--navy",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 309,
      "question": "border-color: #00449e;",
      "answer": "b--dark-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 310,
      "question": "border-color: #357edd;",
      "answer": "b--blue",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 311,
      "question": "border-color: #96ccff;",
      "answer": "b--light-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 312,
      "question": "border-color: #cdecff;",
      "answer": "b--lightest-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 313,
      "question": "border-color: #f6fffe;",
      "answer": "b--washed-blue",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 314,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.9);",
      "answer": "b--black-90",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 315,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.8);",
      "answer": "b--black-80",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 316,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7);",
      "answer": "b--black-70",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 317,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.6);",
      "answer": "b--black-60",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 318,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.5);",
      "answer": "b--black-50",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 319,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.4);",
      "answer": "b--black-40",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 320,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.3);",
      "answer": "b--black-30",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 321,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2);",
      "answer": "b--black-20",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 322,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);",
      "answer": "b--black-10",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 323,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05);",
      "answer": "b--black-05",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 324,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.025);",
      "answer": "b--black-025",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 325,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "b--black-0125",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 326,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.9);",
      "answer": "b--white-90",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 327,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.8);",
      "answer": "b--white-80",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 328,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.7);",
      "answer": "b--white-70",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 329,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.6);",
      "answer": "b--white-60",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 330,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.5);",
      "answer": "b--white-50",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 331,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.4);",
      "answer": "b--white-40",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 332,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.3);",
      "answer": "b--white-30",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 333,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.2);",
      "answer": "b--white-20",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 334,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.1);",
      "answer": "b--white-10",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 335,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.05);",
      "answer": "b--white-05",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 336,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.025);",
      "answer": "b--white-025",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 337,
      "question": "border-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.0125);",
      "answer": "b--white-0125",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 338,
      "question": "border-color: transparent;",
      "answer": "b--transparent",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 339,
      "question": "border-color: inherit;",
      "answer": "b--color-inherit",
      "categories": [
        "Border-color"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-color"
    },
    {
      "id": 340,
      "question": "border-style: solid;",
      "answer": "b--solid",
      "categories": [
        "Border-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 341,
      "question": "border-style: dotted;",
      "answer": "b--dotted",
      "categories": [
        "Border-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 342,
      "question": "border-style: dashed;",
      "answer": "b--dashed",
      "categories": [
        "Border-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 343,
      "question": "border-style: double;",
      "answer": "b--double",
      "categories": [
        "Border-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 344,
      "question": "border-style: groove;",
      "answer": "b--groove",
      "categories": [
        "Border-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 345,
      "question": "border-style: ridge;",
      "answer": "b--ridge",
      "categories": [
        "Border-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 346,
      "question": "border-style: inset;",
      "answer": "b--inset",
      "categories": [
        "Border-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 347,
      "question": "border-style: outset;",
      "answer": "b--outset",
      "categories": [
        "Border-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 348,
      "question": "font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, \"avenir next\", avenir, \"helvetica neue\", helvetica, ubuntu, roboto, noto, \"segoe ui\", arial, sans-serif;",
      "answer": "sans-serif",
      "categories": [
        "Font-family"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-family"
    },
    {
      "id": 349,
      "question": "font-family: georgia, times, serif;",
      "answer": "serif",
      "categories": [
        "Font-family"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-family"
    },
    {
      "id": 350,
      "question": "font-family: consolas, monaco, monospace;",
      "answer": "code",
      "categories": [
        "Font-family"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-family"
    },
    {
      "id": 351,
      "question": "font-family: inherit;",
      "answer": "font-inherit",
      "categories": [
        "Font-family"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-family"
    },
    {
      "id": 352,
      "question": "font-style: normal;",
      "answer": "fs-normal",
      "categories": [
        "Font-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 353,
      "question": "font-style: italic;",
      "answer": "fs-italic",
      "categories": [
        "Font-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 354,
      "question": "font-style: italic;",
      "answer": "i",
      "categories": [
        "Font-style"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-style"
    },
    {
      "id": 355,
      "question": "resize: both;",
      "answer": "resize",
      "categories": [
        "Resize"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#resize"
    },
    {
      "id": 356,
      "question": "resize: horizontal;",
      "answer": "resize-h",
      "categories": [
        "Resize"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#resize"
    },
    {
      "id": 357,
      "question": "resize: vertical;",
      "answer": "resize-v",
      "categories": [
        "Resize"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#resize"
    },
    {
      "id": 358,
      "question": "text-decoration: underline;",
      "answer": "underline",
      "categories": [
        "Text-decoration"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-decoration"
    },
    {
      "id": 359,
      "question": "text-decoration: line-through;",
      "answer": "line-through",
      "categories": [
        "Text-decoration"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-decoration"
    },
    {
      "id": 360,
      "question": "text-decoration: line-through;",
      "answer": "strike",
      "categories": [
        "Text-decoration"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-decoration"
    },
    {
      "id": 361,
      "question": "text-decoration: none;",
      "answer": "no-underline",
      "categories": [
        "Text-decoration"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-decoration"
    },
    {
      "id": 362,
      "question": "text-shadow: 0.1em 0.1em 0.1em rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.6);",
      "answer": "text-shadow",
      "categories": [
        "Text-shadow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-shadow"
    },
    {
      "id": 363,
      "question": "text-transform: capitalize;",
      "answer": "capitalize",
      "categories": [
        "Text-transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 364,
      "question": "text-transform: uppercase;",
      "answer": "uppercase",
      "categories": [
        "Text-transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 365,
      "question": "word-break: break-all;",
      "answer": "word-break-all",
      "categories": [
        "Word-break"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#word-break"
    },
    {
      "id": 366,
      "question": "word-break: break-word;",
      "answer": "word-break-word",
      "categories": [
        "Word-break"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#word-break"
    },
    {
      "id": 367,
      "question": "word-break: normal;",
      "answer": "word-break-normal",
      "categories": [
        "Word-break"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#word-break"
    },
    {
      "id": 368,
      "question": "opacity: 1;",
      "answer": "o-100",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 369,
      "question": "opacity: 0.9;",
      "answer": "o-90",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 370,
      "question": "opacity: 0.8;",
      "answer": "o-80",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 371,
      "question": "opacity: 0.7;",
      "answer": "o-70",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 372,
      "question": "opacity: 0.6;",
      "answer": "o-60",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 373,
      "question": "opacity: 0.5;",
      "answer": "o-50",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 374,
      "question": "opacity: 0.4;",
      "answer": "o-40",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 375,
      "question": "opacity: 0.3;",
      "answer": "o-30",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 376,
      "question": "opacity: 0.2;",
      "answer": "o-20",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 377,
      "question": "opacity: 0.1;",
      "answer": "o-10",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 378,
      "question": "opacity: 0.05;",
      "answer": "o-05",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 379,
      "question": "opacity: 0.025;",
      "answer": "o-025",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 380,
      "question": "opacity: 0;",
      "answer": "o-0",
      "categories": [
        "Opacity"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#opacity"
    },
    {
      "id": 381,
      "question": "transform: translateX(0);",
      "answer": "translateX-0",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 382,
      "question": "transform: translateX(100%);",
      "answer": "translateX-100",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 383,
      "question": "transform: translateX(-100%);",
      "answer": "translateX-n100",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 384,
      "question": "transform: translateX(50%);",
      "answer": "translateX-50",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 385,
      "question": "transform: translateX(-50%);",
      "answer": "translateX-n50",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 386,
      "question": "transform: translateY(0);",
      "answer": "translateY-0",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 387,
      "question": "transform: translateY(100%);",
      "answer": "translateY-100",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 388,
      "question": "transform: translateY(-100%);",
      "answer": "translateY-n100",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 389,
      "question": "transform: translateY(50%);",
      "answer": "translateY-50",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 390,
      "question": "transform: translateY(-50%);",
      "answer": "translateY-n50",
      "categories": [
        "Transform"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transform"
    },
    {
      "id": 391,
      "question": "transition: all 0.5s ease-in-out;",
      "answer": "transition-slow",
      "categories": [
        "Transition"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transition"
    },
    {
      "id": 392,
      "question": "transition: all 0.25s ease-in-out;",
      "answer": "transition-medium",
      "categories": [
        "Transition"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transition"
    },
    {
      "id": 393,
      "question": "transition: all 0.15s ease-in-out;",
      "answer": "transition-fast",
      "categories": [
        "Transition"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transition"
    },
    {
      "id": 394,
      "question": "transition: transform 0.5s ease-in-out;",
      "answer": "transition-transform-slow",
      "categories": [
        "Transition"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transition"
    },
    {
      "id": 395,
      "question": "transition: transform 0.25s ease-in-out;",
      "answer": "transition-transform-medium",
      "categories": [
        "Transition"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transition"
    },
    {
      "id": 396,
      "question": "transition: transform 0.15s ease-in-out;",
      "answer": "transition-transform-fast",
      "categories": [
        "Transition"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#transition"
    },
    {
      "id": 397,
      "question": "visibility: visible;",
      "answer": "visible",
      "categories": [
        "Visibility"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#visibility"
    },
    {
      "id": 398,
      "question": "visibility: hidden;",
      "answer": "hidden",
      "categories": [
        "Visibility"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#visibility"
    },
    {
      "id": 399,
      "question": "visibility: hidden;",
      "answer": "invisible",
      "categories": [
        "Visibility"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#visibility"
    },
    {
      "id": 400,
      "question": "box-shadow: 0 0.125rem 0.5rem 0.125rem rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2);",
      "answer": "shadow-small",
      "categories": [
        "Box-shadow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#box-shadow"
    },
    {
      "id": 401,
      "question": "box-shadow: 0 0.5rem 1rem 0.125rem rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2);",
      "answer": "shadow",
      "categories": [
        "Box-shadow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#box-shadow"
    },
    {
      "id": 402,
      "question": "box-shadow: 0 1rem 2rem 0.25rem rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2);",
      "answer": "shadow-big",
      "categories": [
        "Box-shadow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#box-shadow"
    },
    {
      "id": 403,
      "question": "box-sizing: border-box;",
      "answer": "border-box",
      "categories": [
        "Box-sizing"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#box-sizing"
    },
    {
      "id": 404,
      "question": "box-sizing: content-box;",
      "answer": "content-box",
      "categories": [
        "Box-sizing"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#box-sizing"
    },
    {
      "id": 405,
      "question": "cursor: pointer;",
      "answer": "cursor-pointer",
      "categories": [
        "Cursor"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#cursor"
    },
    {
      "id": 406,
      "question": "cursor: text;",
      "answer": "cursor-text",
      "categories": [
        "Cursor"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#cursor"
    },
    {
      "id": 407,
      "question": "cursor: none;",
      "answer": "cursor-none",
      "categories": [
        "Cursor"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#cursor"
    },
    {
      "id": 408,
      "question": "cursor: not-allowed;",
      "answer": "cursor-not-allowed",
      "categories": [
        "Cursor"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#cursor"
    },
    {
      "id": 409,
      "question": "cursor: progress;",
      "answer": "cursor-progress",
      "categories": [
        "Cursor"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#cursor"
    },
    {
      "id": 410,
      "question": "cursor: wait;",
      "answer": "cursor-wait",
      "categories": [
        "Cursor"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#cursor"
    },
    {
      "id": 411,
      "question": "z-index: 9999;",
      "answer": "z-last",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 412,
      "question": "z-index: -1;",
      "answer": "z-n1",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 413,
      "question": "z-index: 0;",
      "answer": "z-0",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 414,
      "question": "z-index: 1;",
      "answer": "z-1",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 415,
      "question": "z-index: 2;",
      "answer": "z-2",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 416,
      "question": "z-index: 3;",
      "answer": "z-3",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 417,
      "question": "z-index: 4;",
      "answer": "z-4",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 418,
      "question": "z-index: 5;",
      "answer": "z-5",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 419,
      "question": "z-index: 6;",
      "answer": "z-6",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 420,
      "question": "z-index: 7;",
      "answer": "z-7",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 421,
      "question": "z-index: 8;",
      "answer": "z-8",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 422,
      "question": "z-index: 9;",
      "answer": "z-9",
      "categories": [
        "Z-index"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#z-index"
    },
    {
      "id": 423,
      "question": "border-collapse: collapse; border-spacing: 0;",
      "answer": "collapse",
      "categories": [
        "Table"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#table"
    },
    {
      "id": 424,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05);",
      "answer": "stripe-light:nth-child(odd)",
      "categories": [
        "Table"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#table"
    },
    {
      "id": 425,
      "question": "background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);",
      "answer": "stripe-dark:nth-child(odd)",
      "categories": [
        "Table"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#table"
    },
    {
      "id": 426,
      "question": "text-align: left;",
      "answer": "tl",
      "categories": [
        "Text-align"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-align"
    },
    {
      "id": 427,
      "question": "text-align: right;",
      "answer": "tr",
      "categories": [
        "Text-align"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-align"
    },
    {
      "id": 428,
      "question": "text-align: center;",
      "answer": "tc",
      "categories": [
        "Text-align"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-align"
    },
    {
      "id": 429,
      "question": "text-align: justify;",
      "answer": "tj",
      "categories": [
        "Text-align"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#text-align"
    },
    {
      "id": 430,
      "question": "padding: 0;",
      "answer": "p0",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 431,
      "question": "padding: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "p1",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 432,
      "question": "padding: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "p2",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 433,
      "question": "padding: 1rem;",
      "answer": "p3",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 434,
      "question": "padding: 2rem;",
      "answer": "p4",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 435,
      "question": "padding: 4rem;",
      "answer": "p5",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 436,
      "question": "padding: 8rem;",
      "answer": "p6",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 437,
      "question": "padding: 16rem;",
      "answer": "p7",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 438,
      "question": "padding-top: 0;",
      "answer": "pt0",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 439,
      "question": "padding-top: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "pt1",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 440,
      "question": "padding-top: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "pt2",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 441,
      "question": "padding-top: 1rem;",
      "answer": "pt3",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 442,
      "question": "padding-top: 2rem;",
      "answer": "pt4",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 443,
      "question": "padding-top: 4rem;",
      "answer": "pt5",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 444,
      "question": "padding-top: 8rem;",
      "answer": "pt6",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 445,
      "question": "padding-top: 16rem;",
      "answer": "pt7",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 446,
      "question": "padding-right: 0;",
      "answer": "pr0",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 447,
      "question": "padding-right: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "pr1",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 448,
      "question": "padding-right: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "pr2",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 449,
      "question": "padding-right: 1rem;",
      "answer": "pr3",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 450,
      "question": "padding-right: 2rem;",
      "answer": "pr4",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 451,
      "question": "padding-right: 4rem;",
      "answer": "pr5",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 452,
      "question": "padding-right: 8rem;",
      "answer": "pr6",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 453,
      "question": "padding-right: 16rem;",
      "answer": "pr7",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 454,
      "question": "padding-bottom: 0;",
      "answer": "pb0",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 455,
      "question": "padding-bottom: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "pb1",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 456,
      "question": "padding-bottom: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "pb2",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 457,
      "question": "padding-bottom: 1rem;",
      "answer": "pb3",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 458,
      "question": "padding-bottom: 2rem;",
      "answer": "pb4",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 459,
      "question": "padding-bottom: 4rem;",
      "answer": "pb5",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 460,
      "question": "padding-bottom: 8rem;",
      "answer": "pb6",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 461,
      "question": "padding-bottom: 16rem;",
      "answer": "pb7",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 462,
      "question": "padding-left: 0;",
      "answer": "pl0",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 463,
      "question": "padding-left: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "pl1",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 464,
      "question": "padding-left: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "pl2",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 465,
      "question": "padding-left: 1rem;",
      "answer": "pl3",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 466,
      "question": "padding-left: 2rem;",
      "answer": "pl4",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 467,
      "question": "padding-left: 4rem;",
      "answer": "pl5",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 468,
      "question": "padding-left: 8rem;",
      "answer": "pl6",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 469,
      "question": "padding-left: 16rem;",
      "answer": "pl7",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 470,
      "question": "padding-left: 0; padding-right: 0;",
      "answer": "ph0",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 471,
      "question": "padding-left: 0.25rem; padding-right: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "ph1",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 472,
      "question": "padding-left: 0.5rem; padding-right: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "ph2",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 473,
      "question": "padding-left: 1rem; padding-right: 1rem;",
      "answer": "ph3",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 474,
      "question": "padding-left: 2rem; padding-right: 2rem;",
      "answer": "ph4",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 475,
      "question": "padding-left: 4rem; padding-right: 4rem;",
      "answer": "ph5",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 476,
      "question": "padding-left: 8rem; padding-right: 8rem;",
      "answer": "ph6",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 477,
      "question": "padding-left: 16rem; padding-right: 16rem;",
      "answer": "ph7",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 478,
      "question": "padding-top: 0; padding-bottom: 0;",
      "answer": "pv0",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 479,
      "question": "padding-top: 0.25rem; padding-bottom: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "pv1",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 480,
      "question": "padding-top: 0.5rem; padding-bottom: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "pv2",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 481,
      "question": "padding-top: 1rem; padding-bottom: 1rem;",
      "answer": "pv3",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 482,
      "question": "padding-top: 2rem; padding-bottom: 2rem;",
      "answer": "pv4",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 483,
      "question": "padding-top: 4rem; padding-bottom: 4rem;",
      "answer": "pv5",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 484,
      "question": "padding-top: 8rem; padding-bottom: 8rem;",
      "answer": "pv6",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 485,
      "question": "padding-top: 16rem; padding-bottom: 16rem;",
      "answer": "pv7",
      "categories": [
        "Padding"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#padding"
    },
    {
      "id": 486,
      "question": "margin: 0;",
      "answer": "m0",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 487,
      "question": "margin: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "m1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 488,
      "question": "margin: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "m2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 489,
      "question": "margin: 1rem;",
      "answer": "m3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 490,
      "question": "margin: 2rem;",
      "answer": "m4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 491,
      "question": "margin: 4rem;",
      "answer": "m5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 492,
      "question": "margin: 8rem;",
      "answer": "m6",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 493,
      "question": "margin: 16rem;",
      "answer": "m7",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 494,
      "question": "margin-top: 0;",
      "answer": "mt0",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 495,
      "question": "margin-top: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "mt1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 496,
      "question": "margin-top: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "mt2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 497,
      "question": "margin-top: 1rem;",
      "answer": "mt3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 498,
      "question": "margin-top: 2rem;",
      "answer": "mt4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 499,
      "question": "margin-top: 4rem;",
      "answer": "mt5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 500,
      "question": "margin-top: 8rem;",
      "answer": "mt6",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 501,
      "question": "margin-top: 16rem;",
      "answer": "mt7",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 502,
      "question": "margin-top: auto;",
      "answer": "mt-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 503,
      "question": "margin-right: 0;",
      "answer": "mr0",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 504,
      "question": "margin-right: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "mr1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 505,
      "question": "margin-right: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "mr2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 506,
      "question": "margin-right: 1rem;",
      "answer": "mr3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 507,
      "question": "margin-right: 2rem;",
      "answer": "mr4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 508,
      "question": "margin-right: 4rem;",
      "answer": "mr5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 509,
      "question": "margin-right: 8rem;",
      "answer": "mr6",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 510,
      "question": "margin-right: 16rem;",
      "answer": "mr7",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 511,
      "question": "margin-right: auto;",
      "answer": "mr-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 512,
      "question": "margin-bottom: 0;",
      "answer": "mb0",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 513,
      "question": "margin-bottom: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "mb1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 514,
      "question": "margin-bottom: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "mb2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 515,
      "question": "margin-bottom: 1rem;",
      "answer": "mb3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 516,
      "question": "margin-bottom: 2rem;",
      "answer": "mb4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 517,
      "question": "margin-bottom: 4rem;",
      "answer": "mb5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 518,
      "question": "margin-bottom: 8rem;",
      "answer": "mb6",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 519,
      "question": "margin-bottom: 16rem;",
      "answer": "mb7",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 520,
      "question": "margin-bottom: auto;",
      "answer": "mb-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 521,
      "question": "margin-left: 0;",
      "answer": "ml0",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 522,
      "question": "margin-left: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "ml1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 523,
      "question": "margin-left: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "ml2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 524,
      "question": "margin-left: 1rem;",
      "answer": "ml3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 525,
      "question": "margin-left: 2rem;",
      "answer": "ml4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 526,
      "question": "margin-left: 4rem;",
      "answer": "ml5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 527,
      "question": "margin-left: 8rem;",
      "answer": "ml6",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 528,
      "question": "margin-left: 16rem;",
      "answer": "ml7",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 529,
      "question": "margin-left: auto;",
      "answer": "ml-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 530,
      "question": "margin-left: 0; margin-right: 0;",
      "answer": "mh0",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 531,
      "question": "margin-left: 0.25rem; margin-right: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "mh1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 532,
      "question": "margin-left: 0.5rem; margin-right: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "mh2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 533,
      "question": "margin-left: 1rem; margin-right: 1rem;",
      "answer": "mh3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 534,
      "question": "margin-left: 2rem; margin-right: 2rem;",
      "answer": "mh4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 535,
      "question": "margin-left: 4rem; margin-right: 4rem;",
      "answer": "mh5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 536,
      "question": "margin-left: 8rem; margin-right: 8rem;",
      "answer": "mh6",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 537,
      "question": "margin-left: 16rem; margin-right: 16rem;",
      "answer": "mh7",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 538,
      "question": "margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;",
      "answer": "mh-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 539,
      "question": "margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;",
      "answer": "center",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 540,
      "question": "margin-top: 0; margin-bottom: 0;",
      "answer": "mv0",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 541,
      "question": "margin-top: 0.25rem; margin-bottom: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "mv1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 542,
      "question": "margin-top: 0.5rem; margin-bottom: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "mv2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 543,
      "question": "margin-top: 1rem; margin-bottom: 1rem;",
      "answer": "mv3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 544,
      "question": "margin-top: 2rem; margin-bottom: 2rem;",
      "answer": "mv4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 545,
      "question": "margin-top: 4rem; margin-bottom: 4rem;",
      "answer": "mv5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 546,
      "question": "margin-top: 8rem; margin-bottom: 8rem;",
      "answer": "mv6",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 547,
      "question": "margin-top: 16rem; margin-bottom: 16rem;",
      "answer": "mv7",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 548,
      "question": "margin: -0.25rem;",
      "answer": "n1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 549,
      "question": "margin: -0.5rem;",
      "answer": "n2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 550,
      "question": "margin: -1rem;",
      "answer": "n3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 551,
      "question": "margin: -2rem;",
      "answer": "n4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 552,
      "question": "margin: -4rem;",
      "answer": "n5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 553,
      "question": "margin-top: -0.25rem;",
      "answer": "nt1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 554,
      "question": "margin-top: -0.5rem;",
      "answer": "nt2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 555,
      "question": "margin-top: -1rem;",
      "answer": "nt3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 556,
      "question": "margin-top: -2rem;",
      "answer": "nt4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 557,
      "question": "margin-top: -4rem;",
      "answer": "nt5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 558,
      "question": "margin-right: -0.25rem;",
      "answer": "nr1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 559,
      "question": "margin-right: -0.5rem;",
      "answer": "nr2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 560,
      "question": "margin-right: -1rem;",
      "answer": "nr3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 561,
      "question": "margin-right: -2rem;",
      "answer": "nr4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 562,
      "question": "margin-right: -4rem;",
      "answer": "nr5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 563,
      "question": "margin-bottom: -0.25rem;",
      "answer": "nb1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 564,
      "question": "margin-bottom: -0.5rem;",
      "answer": "nb2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 565,
      "question": "margin-bottom: -1rem;",
      "answer": "nb3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 566,
      "question": "margin-bottom: -2rem;",
      "answer": "nb4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 567,
      "question": "margin-bottom: -4rem;",
      "answer": "nb5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 568,
      "question": "margin-left: -0.25rem;",
      "answer": "nl1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 569,
      "question": "margin-left: -0.5rem;",
      "answer": "nl2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 570,
      "question": "margin-left: -1rem;",
      "answer": "nl3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 571,
      "question": "margin-left: -2rem;",
      "answer": "nl4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 572,
      "question": "margin-left: -4rem;",
      "answer": "nl5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 573,
      "question": "margin-left: -0.25rem; margin-right: -0.25rem;",
      "answer": "nh1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 574,
      "question": "margin-left: -0.5rem; margin-right: -0.5rem;",
      "answer": "nh2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 575,
      "question": "margin-left: -1rem; margin-right: -1rem;",
      "answer": "nh3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 576,
      "question": "margin-left: -2rem; margin-right: -2rem;",
      "answer": "nh4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 577,
      "question": "margin-left: -4rem; margin-right: -4rem;",
      "answer": "nh5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 578,
      "question": "margin-top: -0.25rem; margin-bottom: -0.25rem;",
      "answer": "nv1",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 579,
      "question": "margin-top: -0.5rem; margin-bottom: -0.5rem;",
      "answer": "nv2",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 580,
      "question": "margin-top: -1rem; margin-bottom: -1rem;",
      "answer": "nv3",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 581,
      "question": "margin-top: -2rem; margin-bottom: -2rem;",
      "answer": "nv4",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 582,
      "question": "margin-top: -4rem; margin-bottom: -4rem;",
      "answer": "nv5",
      "categories": [
        "Margin"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#margin"
    },
    {
      "id": 583,
      "question": "width: 0;",
      "answer": "w0",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 584,
      "question": "width: 1rem;",
      "answer": "w1",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 585,
      "question": "width: 2rem;",
      "answer": "w2",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 586,
      "question": "width: 4rem;",
      "answer": "w3",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 587,
      "question": "width: 8rem;",
      "answer": "w4",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 588,
      "question": "width: 16rem;",
      "answer": "w5",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 589,
      "question": "width: 32rem;",
      "answer": "w6",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 590,
      "question": "width: 10%;",
      "answer": "w-10",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 591,
      "question": "width: 20%;",
      "answer": "w-20",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 592,
      "question": "width: 25%;",
      "answer": "w-25",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 593,
      "question": "width: 30%;",
      "answer": "w-30",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 594,
      "question": "width: 33.3333333333%;",
      "answer": "w-third",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 595,
      "question": "width: 40%;",
      "answer": "w-40",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 596,
      "question": "width: 50%;",
      "answer": "w-50",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 597,
      "question": "width: 60%;",
      "answer": "w-60",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 598,
      "question": "width: 66.6666666667%;",
      "answer": "w-two-thirds",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 599,
      "question": "width: 70%;",
      "answer": "w-70",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 600,
      "question": "width: 75%;",
      "answer": "w-75",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 601,
      "question": "width: 80%;",
      "answer": "w-80",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 602,
      "question": "width: 90%;",
      "answer": "w-90",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 603,
      "question": "width: 100%;",
      "answer": "w-100",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 604,
      "question": "width: auto;",
      "answer": "w-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 605,
      "question": "width: 25vw;",
      "answer": "vw-25",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 606,
      "question": "width: 50vw;",
      "answer": "vw-50",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 607,
      "question": "width: 75vw;",
      "answer": "vw-75",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 608,
      "question": "width: 100vw;",
      "answer": "vw-100",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 609,
      "question": "min-width: 100vw;",
      "answer": "min-vw-100",
      "categories": [
        "Width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#width"
    },
    {
      "id": 610,
      "question": "max-width: 0;",
      "answer": "mw0",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 611,
      "question": "max-width: 1rem;",
      "answer": "mw1",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 612,
      "question": "max-width: 2rem;",
      "answer": "mw2",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 613,
      "question": "max-width: 4rem;",
      "answer": "mw3",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 614,
      "question": "max-width: 8rem;",
      "answer": "mw4",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 615,
      "question": "max-width: 16rem;",
      "answer": "mw5",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 616,
      "question": "max-width: 32rem;",
      "answer": "mw6",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 617,
      "question": "max-width: 48rem;",
      "answer": "mw7",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 618,
      "question": "max-width: 64rem;",
      "answer": "mw8",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 619,
      "question": "max-width: 96rem;",
      "answer": "mw9",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 620,
      "question": "max-width: 100%;",
      "answer": "mw-100",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 621,
      "question": "max-width: none;",
      "answer": "mw-none",
      "categories": [
        "Max-width"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-width"
    },
    {
      "id": 622,
      "question": "height: 0;",
      "answer": "h0",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 623,
      "question": "height: 1rem;",
      "answer": "h1",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 624,
      "question": "height: 2rem;",
      "answer": "h2",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 625,
      "question": "height: 4rem;",
      "answer": "h3",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 626,
      "question": "height: 8rem;",
      "answer": "h4",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 627,
      "question": "height: 16rem;",
      "answer": "h5",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 628,
      "question": "height: 32rem;",
      "answer": "h6",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 629,
      "question": "height: 0;",
      "answer": "h-0",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 630,
      "question": "height: 25%;",
      "answer": "h-25",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 631,
      "question": "height: 50%;",
      "answer": "h-50",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 632,
      "question": "height: 75%;",
      "answer": "h-75",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 633,
      "question": "height: 100%;",
      "answer": "h-100",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 634,
      "question": "height: auto;",
      "answer": "h-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 635,
      "question": "height: inherit;",
      "answer": "h-inherit",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 636,
      "question": "height: 25vh;",
      "answer": "vh-25",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 637,
      "question": "height: 50vh;",
      "answer": "vh-50",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 638,
      "question": "height: 75vh;",
      "answer": "vh-75",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 639,
      "question": "height: 100vh;",
      "answer": "vh-100",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 640,
      "question": "min-height: 100vh;",
      "answer": "min-vh-100",
      "categories": [
        "Height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#height"
    },
    {
      "id": 641,
      "question": "max-height: 100%;",
      "answer": "mh-100",
      "categories": [
        "Max-height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-height"
    },
    {
      "id": 642,
      "question": "max-height: none;",
      "answer": "mh-none",
      "categories": [
        "Max-height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#max-height"
    },
    {
      "id": 643,
      "question": "position: static;",
      "answer": "static",
      "categories": [
        "Position"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#position"
    },
    {
      "id": 644,
      "question": "position: absolute;",
      "answer": "absolute",
      "categories": [
        "Position"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#position"
    },
    {
      "id": 645,
      "question": "position: relative;",
      "answer": "relative",
      "categories": [
        "Position"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#position"
    },
    {
      "id": 646,
      "question": "position: fixed;",
      "answer": "fixed",
      "categories": [
        "Position"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#position"
    },
    {
      "id": 647,
      "question": "position: sticky;",
      "answer": "sticky",
      "categories": [
        "Position"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#position"
    },
    {
      "id": 648,
      "question": "flex-direction: column;",
      "answer": "flex-column",
      "categories": [
        "Flex-direction"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#flex-direction"
    },
    {
      "id": 649,
      "question": "flex-direction: row;",
      "answer": "flex-row",
      "categories": [
        "Flex-direction"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#flex-direction"
    },
    {
      "id": 650,
      "question": "flex-direction: column-reverse;",
      "answer": "flex-column-reverse",
      "categories": [
        "Flex-direction"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#flex-direction"
    },
    {
      "id": 651,
      "question": "flex-direction: row-reverse;",
      "answer": "flex-row-reverse",
      "categories": [
        "Flex-direction"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#flex-direction"
    },
    {
      "id": 652,
      "question": "display: block;",
      "answer": "db",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 653,
      "question": "display: block;",
      "answer": "block",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 654,
      "question": "display: inline;",
      "answer": "di",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 655,
      "question": "display: inline;",
      "answer": "inline",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 656,
      "question": "display: inline-block;",
      "answer": "dib",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 657,
      "question": "display: inline-block;",
      "answer": "inline-block",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 658,
      "question": "display: none;",
      "answer": "dn",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 659,
      "question": "display: table;",
      "answer": "dt",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 660,
      "question": "display: table-cell;",
      "answer": "dtc",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 661,
      "question": "display: flex;",
      "answer": "df",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 662,
      "question": "display: flex;",
      "answer": "flex",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 663,
      "question": "display: inline-flex;",
      "answer": "dif",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 664,
      "question": "display: inline-flex;",
      "answer": "inline-flex",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 665,
      "question": "display: grid;",
      "answer": "dg",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 666,
      "question": "display: grid;",
      "answer": "grid",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 667,
      "question": "display: contents;",
      "answer": "dc",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 668,
      "question": "display: flow-root;",
      "answer": "dfr",
      "categories": [
        "Display"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#display"
    },
    {
      "id": 669,
      "question": "overflow: visible;",
      "answer": "overflow-visible",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 670,
      "question": "overflow: hidden;",
      "answer": "overflow-hidden",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 671,
      "question": "overflow: scroll;",
      "answer": "overflow-scroll",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 672,
      "question": "overflow: auto;",
      "answer": "overflow-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 673,
      "question": "overflow-x: visible;",
      "answer": "overflow-x-visible",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 674,
      "question": "overflow-x: hidden;",
      "answer": "overflow-x-hidden",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 675,
      "question": "overflow-x: scroll;",
      "answer": "overflow-x-scroll",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 676,
      "question": "overflow-x: auto;",
      "answer": "overflow-x-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 677,
      "question": "overflow-y: visible;",
      "answer": "overflow-y-visible",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 678,
      "question": "overflow-y: hidden;",
      "answer": "overflow-y-hidden",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 679,
      "question": "overflow-y: scroll;",
      "answer": "overflow-y-scroll",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 680,
      "question": "overflow-y: auto;",
      "answer": "overflow-y-auto",
      "categories": [
        "Overflow"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#overflow"
    },
    {
      "id": 681,
      "question": "float: left;",
      "answer": "fl",
      "categories": [
        "Float"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#float"
    },
    {
      "id": 682,
      "question": "float: right;",
      "answer": "fr",
      "categories": [
        "Float"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#float"
    },
    {
      "id": 683,
      "question": "float: none;",
      "answer": "fn",
      "categories": [
        "Float"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#float"
    },
    {
      "id": 684,
      "question": "content: \"\"; display: block; clear: both;",
      "answer": "clearfix::after",
      "categories": [
        "Float"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#float"
    },
    {
      "id": 685,
      "question": "border-radius: 0;",
      "answer": "br0",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 686,
      "question": "border-radius: 0.125rem;",
      "answer": "br1",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 687,
      "question": "border-radius: 0.25rem;",
      "answer": "br2",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 688,
      "question": "border-radius: 0.5rem;",
      "answer": "br3",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 689,
      "question": "border-radius: 1rem;",
      "answer": "br4",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 690,
      "question": "border-radius: 100%;",
      "answer": "br-100",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 691,
      "question": "border-radius: 99999px;",
      "answer": "br-pill",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 692,
      "question": "border-bottom-right-radius: 0; border-bottom-left-radius: 0;",
      "answer": "br--top",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 693,
      "question": "border-top-left-radius: 0; border-bottom-left-radius: 0;",
      "answer": "br--right",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 694,
      "question": "border-top-right-radius: 0; border-top-left-radius: 0;",
      "answer": "br--bottom",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 695,
      "question": "border-top-right-radius: 0; border-bottom-right-radius: 0;",
      "answer": "br--left",
      "categories": [
        "Border-radius"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#border-radius"
    },
    {
      "id": 696,
      "question": "font-size: 6rem;",
      "answer": "f-headline",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 697,
      "question": "font-size: 5rem;",
      "answer": "f-subheadline",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 698,
      "question": "font-size: 3.0517578125em;",
      "answer": "f1",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 699,
      "question": "font-size: 2.44140625em;",
      "answer": "f2",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 700,
      "question": "font-size: 1.953125em;",
      "answer": "f3",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 701,
      "question": "font-size: 1.5625em;",
      "answer": "f4",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 702,
      "question": "font-size: 1.25em;",
      "answer": "f5",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 703,
      "question": "font-size: 1em;",
      "answer": "f6",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 704,
      "question": "font-size: 0.8em;",
      "answer": "small",
      "categories": [
        "Font-size"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-size"
    },
    {
      "id": 705,
      "question": "line-height: 1;",
      "answer": "lh-solid",
      "categories": [
        "Line-height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#line-height"
    },
    {
      "id": 706,
      "question": "line-height: 1.15;",
      "answer": "lh-title",
      "categories": [
        "Line-height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#line-height"
    },
    {
      "id": 707,
      "question": "line-height: 1.5;",
      "answer": "lh-copy",
      "categories": [
        "Line-height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#line-height"
    },
    {
      "id": 708,
      "question": "line-height: 2;",
      "answer": "lh-extra",
      "categories": [
        "Line-height"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#line-height"
    },
    {
      "id": 709,
      "question": "font-weight: 100;",
      "answer": "fw-100",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 710,
      "question": "font-weight: 200;",
      "answer": "fw-200",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 711,
      "question": "font-weight: 300;",
      "answer": "fw-300",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 712,
      "question": "font-weight: 400;",
      "answer": "fw-400",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 713,
      "question": "font-weight: 500;",
      "answer": "fw-500",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 714,
      "question": "font-weight: 600;",
      "answer": "fw-600",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 715,
      "question": "font-weight: 700;",
      "answer": "fw-700",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 716,
      "question": "font-weight: 800;",
      "answer": "fw-800",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 717,
      "question": "font-weight: 900;",
      "answer": "fw-900",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 718,
      "question": "font-weight: lighter;",
      "answer": "fw-lighter",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 719,
      "question": "font-weight: bolder;",
      "answer": "fw-bolder",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 720,
      "question": "font-weight: 400;",
      "answer": "fw-normal",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 721,
      "question": "font-weight: 700;",
      "answer": "b",
      "categories": [
        "Font-weight"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 722,
      "question": "white-space: nowrap;",
      "answer": "nowrap",
      "categories": [
        "White-space"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#white-space"
    },
    {
      "id": 723,
      "question": "white-space: pre;",
      "answer": "pre",
      "categories": [
        "White-space"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#white-space"
    },
    {
      "id": 724,
      "question": "white-space: pre-wrap;",
      "answer": "pre-wrap",
      "categories": [
        "White-space"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#white-space"
    },
    {
      "id": 725,
      "question": "vertical-align: middle;",
      "answer": "v-mid",
      "categories": [
        "Vertical-align"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#vertical-align"
    },
    {
      "id": 726,
      "question": "vertical-align: middle;",
      "answer": "v-middle",
      "categories": [
        "Vertical-align"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#vertical-align"
    },
    {
      "id": 727,
      "question": "vertical-align: top;",
      "answer": "v-top",
      "categories": [
        "Vertical-align"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#vertical-align"
    },
    {
      "id": 728,
      "question": "vertical-align: bottom;",
      "answer": "v-bottom",
      "categories": [
        "Vertical-align"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#vertical-align"
    },
    {
      "id": 729,
      "question": "letter-spacing: 0.1em;",
      "answer": "tracked",
      "categories": [
        "Letter-spacing"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#letter-spacing"
    },
    {
      "id": 730,
      "question": "letter-spacing: -0.05em;",
      "answer": "tracked-tight",
      "categories": [
        "Letter-spacing"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#letter-spacing"
    },
    {
      "id": 731,
      "question": "letter-spacing: 0.25em;",
      "answer": "tracked-mega",
      "categories": [
        "Letter-spacing"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#letter-spacing"
    },
    {
      "id": 732,
      "question": "max-width: 20em;",
      "answer": "measure-narrow",
      "categories": [
        "Measure"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#measure"
    },
    {
      "id": 733,
      "question": "max-width: 30em;",
      "answer": "measure",
      "categories": [
        "Measure"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#measure"
    },
    {
      "id": 734,
      "question": "max-width: 34em;",
      "answer": "measure-wide",
      "categories": [
        "Measure"
      ],
      "url": "https://c4s.cdijkman.nl/example.html#measure"
    }
  ]
};